Produced by AZER
Lena
what?
Tomorrow's work
Lena, I'm sorry.
Because I'm not making much money
I made the leader do too much.
Are you okay
Because we're a married couple
We have to help each other.
And
Because it's fun and easy
That's good then
It's been three years since we got married.
The two of them are living a happy married life.
But I was hiding something from my husband.
Wow, that's amazing! You're number one again!
thank you
I've been a nanpawan since I joined the store.
It's already a milestone in the history of our store.
Is that so? I'm happy.
Keep it up, I hope you'll continue supporting me this month.
I bought a house last year
At that timing
My husband passed and was mentioned.
I have a lot of money to pay for my house.
Good income
I decided to work at Soplan.
To my husband
He lies about it being a sexual training job.
I'm looking forward to having kids
That's right
Is it moving yet?
It's only been a month so I'm not moving yet
That's right
Let's get married
Every single day, every single day
You promised me you wouldn't do it until the baby was born.
I haven't done it even once since I found out I was pregnant.
I can't stand it.
No, hold on.
Got it
Speaking of which
There was a senior girl named Rena who I used to be close with.
Recently, I contacted him for the first time in a while.
There was a octopus living really close by.
So we ended up playing with each other's breasts.
Can I call you home?
Yes
please
Thank you. It's been a while.
How many years has it been?
It's been 10 years
Has it been that long?
It hasn't changed at all.
The layers haven’t changed at all either.
Recently I did this
About 3 months ago
Amazing, I've always been here
Ah, how many years has it been?
Well, maybe five or six years.
Atka mackerel I see
I bought a house.
That
Oh no
Nice
still
Not yet
It's going to be hard from now on
I have kids after all.
Feeling like
That's right.
Congratulations, right?
Amazing!
Because I'm useless
but
I just wanted a child.
I moved because my previous house was too noisy.
The timing is...
Are you used to it around here?
Aren't supermarkets a little expensive?
Eh! Expensive?!
Was that place too cheap?
Ah, really.
Right there
Ah, yes, a bit expensive.
Big shop on the other side
So maybe I'll go there then.
Maybe that would be cheaper.
Are there any good restaurants around here?
It's delicious... Oh! There are quite a lot of them.
What do you think?
Let's go for lunch next time
Ah, that's basically it.
It's easier to get out during the day
Recently there's a pizza place in front of the station.
Ah, Mr. Pisayan, I've never been there.
It's always lined up
Yes. It's hard to get in because there's a line.
Yeah, let's go.
Let's go
So you're still not with your husband around here?
That's right.
I moved and had a lot of trouble.
That's right, I'm still not calm
I'll enjoy having this
It was a little hot
Hey, if you say so
What kind of person is Tanzo?
What is it?
That's so kind.
That's kind, I like it
I feel like I've become even kinder since having a child.
Are you naturally kind?
Yeah. It's kind, but it feels kind of nice.
I'm jealous!
My house is completely different now.
Is that true?
Karan has been with me for about five years.
Long thread
Is your house natural?
But if he's nice, then it's okay, right?
Do you not usually fight?
I feel like I've surpassed that already.
Is it getting cold?
Thank you
Sorry to bother you
I'd like to introduce you to Rena, who I spoke to yesterday.
Oh, thank you for your help.
Nice to meet you
Please take your time.
thank you
Are you okay? Husband
I feel like it's totally fine.
It's true, it seems sturdy and gentle.
Is that true?
That's nice, I'm jealous
Next time I meet Rena's Danzo
Yes, absolutely. Please come and visit us.
I want to go
It's definitely stylish.
That's not true. I totally agree.
Is that true?
The interior design used to be quite elaborate, didn't it?
Ah! Mingkai is
But after I got married,
Oh yeah
Life after all...
It will change a little bit.
Certainly.
I want to look a little more stylish, but I'm not sure.
It's difficult, isn't it?
Oh, really. I want to dress up a bit more.
But it's just beginning
I haven't even put away the cardboard boxes yet.
No, it's not that hard if you're pregnant.
Not quite there yet
But somehow it hasn't grown much.
Keiko
what
Next week, Saturday and Sunday are consecutive holidays.
Should I go somewhere?
Yes, I want to go.
Well, I'll look for it.
thank you
Let's practice
I'm telling you, no.
Please, just once
No
Soap?
sorry
Just once
Sorry for the wait
Have fun today too
The room is here
thank you
Well then, excuse me.
nice to meet you
It's Rena right?
Wrong.
It's definitely Rena
How do you end up working in a place like this?
Umm...
Please keep this a secret
Of course. I want to wear something like this and see the back.
Seriously... please keep it a secret
It's okay! I keep my promises.
But why?
Please don't listen to that
Let's stop talking darkly
I came all the way here with my customers.
Oh, you have to enjoy it a lot. I'll be happy to serve you.
Let's get started
I'm kind of nervous.
Do you come to places like this often?
This is the first time since we got married.
That's right
Did you come a lot before you got married?
Well, that too... occasionally.
How is the practice going?
Not from the new birth
Well then, I'm trying my best
oh dear
Did you never touch her boobs?
Well, yes
Is it because he's a baby?
♪ Music
It hurts so much
I'm so shocked.
Don't you want to do something more pleasurable?
Ah, I like it.
So, should we go to Matt?
Hey, let's play again
Let's go
Ah! Yes!
Is it okay? It's hot.
it's okay
Is this Matt's first time?
Yes, Matato is the first
I'm looking forward to it.
It's not cold
Are you okay
It's so slippery though
It feels strange.
Slipping again
You don't do this if you oversleep.
I can't
Is this okay?
What it feels like
The feeling was good
Sleepy, true
Was it just normal sex with Keiko?
- Practice.
No, that's... normal.
There's something wrong.
Eh, what is it like?
I wonder what kind of sex they have
I'm curious.
Are you okay
Ahh! Feels good
Yes, okay.
I'll win a lot of New Year's money
Did you get a rice ball?
It has already arrived in the meantime
That's true...
It's beautiful, isn't it?
thank you
I thought it was a thin time
No, I just happened to see a lot of different things.
There are quite a few
I can't say for sure.
Y-yes.
Do you like bread?
Yes, I like it.
nice
Are you rubbing your neck?
The head is easy to understand
Let's definitely try it
I remember your funny face
This is my first time
Who has never drunk it?
Is it ticklish?
No, it's really good.
She's dressed in a naughty way.
It's turned into a terrible powder.
A very horny old man
Are you touching everything?
hot
Where does it feel good?
1cm left in all
here
It's so annoying.
Hold on a cup
Are you okay
My body wants to do that.
Where is this being assigned?
In the back
Amazing! You've really taken the time
You're starting to get excited now.
Your feet are big
Ah, it's delicious.
Are you tired?
I was surprised
Can you lie on your back next time?
If we continue like this, we won't be able to see anything anymore
Lend me a hand
I'll help you.
Wow, it's become like this now
Because it's slippery
I'm getting stuck
Wow, it's been ringing like this for a day.
Did you see this?
I can see your ass
Wow, that's amazing.
Okay, put it in.
delicious
Grandpa, you are ethics
sorry
It makes it easier for my waist to be pinched.
Feeling hungry?
Doesn't it hurt??
The motion is slippery
Does it feel good?
Ah, yes.
After all, if you come to Softland, you want to get in, right?
No... already
Can I put it in this?
I'm glad it's the way it is
Keep it on
This is what happens
So the entrance is just like this.
Let's do it
It's so big!
here?
Oh, I walked in next to it.
this is···
It's in the back. Kinky is big.
This one too...
How clicked is it?
It's amazing!
Because it's so cool.
Hey, you can put it in here
Just like this forever
It's really hard, Teatin said.
Only the hands are in
- I can type everything
There's a burr
One more left
I want you to follow me from behind
Is it me?
I will do my best
It's dangerous so be careful
Wow, amazing!
Hey, feels good
Sorry, can you help me?
wait a minute
First sex feeling
This is the last one
Become a lot stronger
amazing
There
I'm not tired
amazing
Ah, it's hot.
Sweet and different?
Should I put it in every time?
☀Did it feel good? Yes
Please come again anytime.
I've been waiting for you
By the way, haven't they been talking about specifications lately?
Oh no, well, look.
Myself, come on.
I thought it was selfish of me so I decided to just put up with it.
thank you
By the way, Rena is coming again this weekend. Is that okay?
Huh... ah... huh...?
Ah yeah. It's okay.
Sorry for coming back again
Please wear it anytime.
thank you
I might actually go because I'm really bored.
I'm bored too.
Please feel free to come anytime.
it was good
The tea looks delicious
Isn't this tea really delicious?
Is that true? There's a store in front of the station that always has a line.
I bought it there
Even though there was a huge line
Yes, I always had to line up, so I couldn't buy it.
I'm still worried and trying my best
But it's very delicious
Really?
I can't stand it anymore
good morning.
Really delicious!
Would you like another serving?
Can I have it?
Thank you, sorry
It's totally fine
Let's go shopping
Okay.
please
Please, you don't have to go.
No, no, it's right there.
Because Asaka is lining up
it's okay
No, it's not okay? Because I'm pregnant.
Me too
I want to drink it again
It's really okay
Well then, I'm off.
Please wait
Don't push yourself
that's right
Because it's right there
sorry
You're silent.
Of course.
Thank you for keeping your promise
Wh-what are you doing?
I kept my promise
But...
No, already, that
After all, I was married.
Are you okay
There's a huge line of tea shops over there.
That's right.
There's nothing else like it.
Ah, yes.
Won't you let me do it from now on?
Well… yes
So take it off.
Are you sure?
It's okay, Keiko. She hasn't come home yet.
You've been found out, right?
Because it has become like this
By the time you arrived,
If it gets found out, things will be bad.
It's okay, you won't get caught
I just went there.
You'll definitely have to queue for 30 minutes there
30 minutes
It's become like this
But outside of the store,
It's okay. I was the one who fooled you today.
sorry
It won't go down
Look! I've been waiting this long.
Poor thing, they don't let you do what you want.
Is your hair getting stiff?
what happened
I have a feeling that something bad will happen.
It was a big problem.
I didn't really touch it much at the store, did I?
on second thoughts…
Nasty hand gestures
I'll do this like crazy.
Do you want to have this dick pinched?
It's not slimy, but it's fine today.
I'll put it in here for you, teen
please
It's become a bed
Before you go to bed in the morning, try tasting Grandpa.
Amazing hip movement
Doesn't it feel weird at home?
What it feels like
Usually, I die in a place like this.
You're crying, right?
What, where are you crying?
It's a bedroom
You can put your hand in
please
Feels good
Are you nervous?
Yeah, I'm nervous.
Because it's my house
no
In your own home
He acts all high and mighty.
It's amazing, see?
It's getting bigger and bigger
It has become
Can you drink it?
Where does it feel good?
Stacked on my chest
Today, as a thank you, I'll give you something nice
kitchen?
here
Damn
Sigh
Sky shore
I cut off Bandara.
After
half
hot
terrible
Hit me
Ah, you're following me, right? I'm behind you.
Awesome!
It's so hard and hard!
If that happens, I'll go right away
That's fine. Let out what you've been saving up.
Wow, amazing!
Very scary
Eh?
Ah, it feels good
It feels so good
Wow, amazing!
Really, no.
There are so many!
It's dripping
That's a great nose
Did it feel good?
If you come to our store, we'll give you even more service.
I'm glad you came again
I want to meet Rena too.
I won't change the things I don't like
If I don't let it happen anymore
I'm going to do a lot of isavish today
It started to feel good.
Wash your body.
please
Give me your legs!
It's fresh.
Really? You wouldn't do something like this
I have never done it.
I'm also practicing.
Sometimes we take a bath together
Totally cute
Do you sometimes take a bath?
I agree
How does it feel?
If they're together, I guess they'll wash them.
I don't wash it
Is that so?
I'm moving and it's going to be smaller
Because the room is spacious
Oh, really? The bathtub was big before too.
Have you ever been treated like this before?
What does it feel like?
Very hot
Warm
No, it's hot.
What is hitting?
I'll wash this one too.
Lend it to the other hand
Well then, this time from here
Is it hot here too?
Ah, it's too hot
Even after it dries, it's starting to feel dull
That's amazing.
What do you think?
While it's still warm,
Feeling
I wonder if it's beautiful now
But you have to wash your back too.
Feels good?
I'll make everything beautiful
Ah, yes.
Finally, we have to wash the important parts.
Look at that! And it's become like this.
Ah, yes.
Is there anything else I'm missing?
it's okay
Removes cleanly
I'll warm it up next time
This feels really good
Do you like it?
How's your ass?
It's really good
Wow, it's getting lukewarm.
Do you get creepy?
No, it gives me goosebumps.
Can I add more water?
Let me hold it in my hand
Now I need a good wash
I'm washing
If you keep doing it like this, will you do it while wet?
Huu-chin-chan, get wet.
Wow, that feels good
This also feels good
That's a stupid mistake
It smells good
Can be produced in large quantities
sorry
I love you
It felt so good.
Can you still get it out today?
Of course!
But it's extremely brilliant
That's because Rena is attractive.
Well then, shall I go to the bathroom and rinse?
Wait a minute, get well soon
I am very satisfied.
It has a spicy and sweet taste
What are your feelings?
To express the greatness of it,
Can I play with your boobs?
Ah, yes.
Shall I touch it?
Ah, so much.
It felt good
It's so solid
Ahh, it feels good
Does it feel good?
Boobs?
Oh, that's so unfair.
Hmm, huh?
I want to feel better
I want to put
May I
Well, I'll put it in.
Swoosh
Hey, Reinan
Haven't you done it recently?
Do you sometimes
sorry
I've been busy and tired lately
Ah… that’s right.
I felt fulfilled thanks to Ken.
And at some point, I started looking forward to Ken's visit.
I'm home
This is you, Reina.
Huh? No, what's that?
I fell here
Not me though
If it's not you then who?
You've been coming home late lately.
Well, a little
Do you think you'll spend such a night at a normal job?
Well, there were a lot of things
What do you mean by various things?
Well, there are a lot of them.
What are you hiding?
I'm not hiding anything.
What does this mean?
It's strange that this fell
Not mine
Don't get angry
To be honest
I'm sorry
Actually, I had no choice because of my home loan.
But why is it like that?
Thank you very much everyone
I was doing a lot of things.
Home loans
Because I wanted to make my life with you more fun
This was the place where there was no salary.
I'm really sorry.
Sorry, you
Really trash
Forgive me
I'm really sorry.
Really, inside
radar
It's bad that I don't earn much
That's not true.
I'm a substitute
Yeah. I'm quitting my job.
Lena
But I can't do it suddenly, so please let me come to work this week.
I get it, but it really should be the last one
I'd like to ask for more service today
Well, you see
what's wrong?
Actually, it's good
My husband found out about this job.
So today is my last day at work.
That's right
Don't make such a sad face
Today is the last day
So I'll give you lots of service.
Hey, now put on a smile
Is it okay if it's the last one?
Laugh
Sorry
It's delicious
Feels good?
It really makes me feel better
amazing
Huh?
What do you want?
I want you to feel good with Russian
Try that
So do what you love
Well then, let's have a slippery drink.
I'm going to sleep, so my stomach is warm.
Are you okay?
This one too
Let's go to the feet
Does it not feel good at all where your boobs are touching you?
Can't you do this at home?
Just do your best.
You're dressed so sexy.
Chi-chin is awake
It's getting bigger
I'll be fine soon
Sit Down
How about something like this?
Ah, it's so slippery
Ah, what a naughty look
This is a very good Eve.
I'm soaked now
Does it hurt?
I want to touch it
Okay, touch it.
Slimy body
be careful
Are you okay?
It's so slippery
It's different from the usual irresistible
This is the last one, so I'll do my best
amazing
I slept too long
Ah, it feels good
feel?
I can get it
Oh, that's good
delicious
Wow, what a slimy smell
I drink
Ahh, feels good!
Ah, it feels good
Wow
Hmm...
Hey, I want to put it in
Well, I put it in
Hmm.
I'll put my hands on the sure thing
Ah, is it okay to make Tensel soft?
This is still big
Diaclean is vomiting
It's so crunchy!
The breath is hitting
It's a little hard
Very hard
Ahh, that feels good!
Hit the bed
over there
Hmm...
Squeak
Aaaah
high
open
Han
Oh
go
GO
I'm coming
Hmm.
good
me too
It felt good
Fufu
Wow
Ah, I'm tired.
It was close but fun
Me too.
hey
Huh?
everyone
Has it already entered a stable period?
I agree
Well, let's do it.
I told you not to until the baby is born.
Understood
Should I go to a soapland for the first time in a while?
I'm so sorry
So, please have fun today too.
The room is here
Excuse me
It's Ena, have fun today
Why?
You came here to have fun today
Next time you feel horny, come over anytime
Produced by AZER