Ryu-chan
I got breakfast
I'll enjoy having this
Hard fried egg opened and said
Overcooked mom
Yu-chan looks sleepy
The school is still dim
Usseewa this earth
Go out somewhere
Where does it matter
Wait a minute, fried egg
Yesterday I got a call from her dad next week
I made a note that I'm coming back with a picture of my child
Hikikomori, you
Withdrawal in Manken's club room Eh Kaito's Manma Now
Hashiguchi is a little old
Unlike you, it's hard to go to a prep school, isn't it?
Well that's right
She needs a break, she doesn't even have her now
I contacted you when I was free
I don't know what to do, she's a game
You now she
I used to know it when I was in high school.
Well, my parents are strict
There were various things like coming home at 7 pm, after all
It ’s only after she graduated, that ’s not the case.
The pride that she was the most popular in Manken of all time
Unlike you guys, she's like that and chicken
Not yet
But also for Saryusuke
I don't think that was the case with you
It was kind, she didn't speak at all, she wasn't even in the Soviet Union
If you force me, why
I'm scared of my eyes
All my father's fireballs are two
My mother's family is all alone
Sena is now in our class Kubogi
The child you liked seems to have got married
Well, I was on good terms with that cute girl for a while.
I always said she had Yusuke's eyes
A little scary
Help me a little, what's she doing?
It's all because of Abukawa
Especially she has this email
This scene of mine
The worst of following me
It's all because of him
I'm back
Grandpa is curry today
it is cold today
What happened
Why is this face
Is it wrong?
Always
I want to write a little
Nagaokakyo
Hey
Maeda Arena
A little bit
Why did I give birth to such a face?
I'm a club activity failure
sorry Sorry
Nagano Prefecture
It's your fault
sorry
Nice
Why did you do this?
Google flowers
I understand
Be quiet
A little
Your fault
Kanda Pirates
I'm sorry she is
What are you doing
You should do this and she should be quiet
Cat litter
You're bad
I'm not a mother
I'm sorry
Donna
It's your fault
why
Can't move
do not look at me
Because there is a rice cooker
Mom
She has to go to the part
Goodbye type
CD does not make more sound
high school
That yourself
Hey soon
But it can be used
Horse racing forecast
Yes Yes
Tamagawadai Park
Shimoda ship
Selfish curse
Last kind
That's like this
quickly
I'll be back a little longer
I decide
Faster
Handicraft shop
Do this
Use your head
quickly
disposable
Can be used a lot
Marmot
Night Ray
interesting
Open your mouth
Salmon painting
Salmon ramen
From Hiratsuka
Wall clock
Give me more
Put it in the house
Basics
Erotic
sorry
It's raining
You see
Kyu-chan
I'm going to the part
Why i
Akaoni
Spider liner
Golf samurai
Dad I didn't like love
Don't talk about chopsticks
Properly
Sleeping
Daiso
Choreography
Korankei
Laundry storage
You can have this
That's it
Oh yeah yeah
hello
She hasn't told her if she's going to school with Arisa
I think he will say that
This is because you don't take it as a mother and as a parent without me
excuse me
For the time being, I'll be riding the first Shinkansen the morning after tomorrow, so will I speak firmly when I return?
Laundry storage
I'll bring that
Because it ’s the day my dad will come back tomorrow.
Such a thing
What's wrong
How much do you shift your mother?
That kind of girlfriend is sick
If you are not a parent
I was able to walk a normal life
What are you hitting
I'm sorry Ryu-chan
I am really sorry
I'm sorry she has a bad mom
But she wants a child as a mother
My dad told me not to make it
She just couldn't give up
When Ryu-chan was made
I was happy
Mom
Give up
I didn't let you
I am really sorry
Someone like you
Touch
White teeth
Shiro
storm
Properly
Mom
sorry
Does not heal
Shin-chan and mom
Doing with mom
I'm sorry I thought it was a failure
sorry
Just in a house like this
University is not free
Almost always you
Isn't it bad because you're not disciplined?
I'm leaving the house to you
But I'm in trouble without her
I work outside
I'm paying for my living expenses
Mom not bad
Any attitude
Your next calendar is too spoiled
Omaehama Bridge
Ryusuke is the only son, so I have to protect him firmly.
Isn't it only you? Adults