Well, why are you looking at me like that?
Look, I know, I know, I know.
I know we got into it.
You were annoying me.
But I wanna play.
Can't you tell?
Well, aren't you gonna say anything?
Or do I have to come over there and do all the talking?
Well, I don't mind.
Is it better to talk here?
God, you're quiet tonight.
I'm so horny.
Oh my god.
I can't explain it.
Come on.
I want you.
And haven't you noticed?
Wearing my special daddy's girl outfit.
Cause you know that I love it when you're my daddy.
And right now, daddy, I'm aching.
I need to be fucked.
What do you mean?
Yeah, so what?
I'm a little tipsy.
Who cares?
You don't mind, don't you daddy?
Don't you wanna put your hands all over your daughter?
Your daughter?
Yeah, I know you do.
I just love it.
My daddy fucks me so good.
Come on daddy.
I want you.
Look.
See?
I want you bad.
So bad.
Come on daddy.
Oh my god.
I said who cares?
If I'm a little drunk.
This girl wants her daddy.
Oh, you want me too, don't you daddy?
Oh, I can tell just how badly you want your sweet little girl.
Isn't that right daddy?
I'm gonna kiss ya.
You wanna feel my sweet, wet, juicy lips on your big daddy cock.
See, I knew you weren't gonna be able to I mean, I wasn't kidding.
It is a big, huge daddy cock.
It's kinda hard to fit you in my mouth daddy.
Maybe I just need to open wider.
You wanna watch me open wider for you daddy?
That's it daddy.
You love it don't you?
When your sweet little daughter gets so sloppy, so messy.
God, you taste so good today daddy.
You're so big, so thick.
It's in your cock.
What a big daddy penis.
Stretching my mouth so wide.
Daddy.
I love tasting your pre-cum.
Knowing how much you want me.
Isn't that right daddy?
You want me so bad.
You can't even handle it.
Come on daddy, tell me.
Don't you love it when your daughter plays with your dick?
Come on daddy say it.
Tell me that you love it when your daughter plays with your dick.
You're close aren't you daddy?
I can tell.
You're throbbing.
Oh my god.
My hand.
I can't even close around your face.
Look at how big it is.
You taste so good.
So manly.
I guess I've forgotten what it's like to taste my dad's penis.
Daddy you know I'm a good girl.
I've never done anything like this.
But I want you to be the first.
Now you heard me right daddy.
I want you to come in my mouth.
Come on come in your daughter's mouth.
I've never tasted any man's cum before.
But I want you to be the first.
Say yes daddy.
Daddy I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
Oh Jesus.
Daddy that was...
Massive load.
God, you just tasted, I don't know, so much more mature.
Maybe I am more tipsy than I thought.
Want me to clean you up, daddy?
There you go.
Boy...
You are still hard.
We never go again.
What's with you tonight?
Something's funny.
I mean, it's kind of hot that...
You are still rock fucking hard.
You must really like it.
Put your daughter head in store for you.
Maybe we can go again.
Would you like that?
Would my daddy like that?
I think that's a yes.
Well...
Alright then.
Fuck me daddy.
Fuck me with this big throbbing dick.
Please?
Daddy, I am so wet for you.
I can't wait for you to feel it.
But first I should probably take these off.
So you can fit.
There daddy.
I am ready.
Oh my god.
It's really hard to fit.
You are so deep daddy.
Have you ever been this deep inside me?
I just feel you.
Just hitting my G spot over and over again.
I just want to get all of you.
I can barely stretch wide enough.
To fit you and my tight little hole daddy.
Can you believe it?
That you are inside me.
Your big daddy dick.
Is inside me.
I want you to fit all the way.
Oh daddy.
Oh my god.
Oh fuck I am going to cum.
Oh daddy.
I can't believe you made me cum.
You never make me cum like that.
I guess.
When you are my daddy.
Things are different aren't they?
Oh my god.
It's like you are a new man.
The way that you are stretching me.
I never felt you go in this deep before.
Well daddy.
This is.
The only cock that I am ever going to fuck.
I am yours daddy.
That's only my.
My pussy.
For my daddy.
This is the only cock that I want.
I only want my daddy's cock.
My daddy's big.
Perfect dick.
Oh fuck.
Oh my daddy.
So deep daddy.
I feel you.
In my belly.
Speaking of my belly.
Daddy.
You are finally going to give me that baby that I have always wanted.
Oh come on daddy.
Please say yes.
Finally.
I am going to fill my womb.
With your sperm.
My daddy's sperm.
Daddy.
You know.
I am ovulating.
Yeah daddy.
My body is ready to make your baby.
Are you finally going to give me a baby daddy?
Yeah be my baby daddy.
Give me a baby daddy.
Please.
I am so fertile.
So much so that.
I feel your pregum dripping inside me.
Maybe.
You have already given me a baby.
Daddy.
That's it daddy.
Faster.
Fuck daddy.
You are so deep inside me.
I feel you.
Your cock.
And so all the way up to my cervix.
Oh daddy.
We are so close please.
Please give me a baby daddy.
Please make.
My big juicy titties.
Fill up with milk.
Make me pregnant.
Give me a baby daddy.
Yeah.
I want to come daddy.
Daddy come.
Give me a baby daddy.
Please.
Fuck you coming to me.
Daddy come.
Come inside me.
Make me come.
I feel so good.
To have an orgasm.
My pussy is wrapped around.
Oh my daddy's cock.
Daddy stay.
Daddy stay please.
Keep pumping hard.
Oh.
Yeah.
Let's make sure.
Oh.
You give me a baby.
Oh my god.
Oh.
I think that definitely did it.
Mmm.
Oh.
Oh well.
Oh god.
Mmm.
Really tipsy.
Okay.
Honey.
I gotta go get cleaned up okay?
Yeah.
Oh.
Oh my god.
Where am I?
Of course our bed.
Hey honey.
Well.
How did you sleep?
Especially after what we did last night.
What do you mean we didn't do anything last night?
You're crazy.
We definitely had sex.
I let you come in my mouth for Christ sakes.
What do you mean you don't remember?
Of course it happened.
I'm dressed.
Oh.
What do you mean I just conked out in bed next to you?
What?
Wearing this?
Yeah.
After we fucked.
Are you being serious right now?
I mean my panties are gone.
What the fuck?
I mean I definitely had sex last night.
I know.
We have a house full of people.
I mean that's what happens when you have a party and guests drink too much.
They stay over.
You don't think I...
Come on.
I would never do that to you.
Look I don't know maybe maybe I'll go to my dad's room.
Maybe he knows what happened.
Where's my rope?
Are you sure you're not messing with me?
Well because I'm about to go wake my dad up.
To ask him if he knows anything about I don't know.
Anything suspicious that happened last night.
There were a lot of people over.
Well yeah I'm still going to go ask him.
We'll be back.
Hey dad.
Yeah.
I know you're in the shower.
I just wanted to come by because I have a question for you.
Yeah.
It is about last night.
What happened last night?
Well I know I just I woke up this morning and I mean I knew that I had had sex.
Obviously I thought it was with my husband but coming here to your room and I mean it reeks of sex in here.
And finding these.
My panties.
God I was so stupid.
No this is all my fault dad.
I I didn't mean for this to happen.
I guess I just must have been so far gone.
I had one too many drinks and no I mean I remember I remember a lot.
I just don't remember it actually being with you dad.
And of course no don't don't apologize look it was a one time thing okay so it happened and there's nothing we can do about that now and it was wrong.
So taboo.
Oh god.
To risk this I mean what if we were caught?
Practically all of our family is here.
Somewhere in this house.
Look I just I just think we call it what it was.
A mistake.
Right?
Right daddy?
Oh god I just I can't believe it you know.
It would be hard to forget what happened between us I mean it was I just I've never experienced anything like that before.
You neither?
You mean all the things that I was saying?
That it was the best sex of my life?
That I was obsessed and in love with your cock?
I mean I have to admit those things are true.
Just thinking about the way that you fit inside me.
I mean just the fact that right now actually literally full of your cum full of my dad's cum.
I know what's wrong.
I know I shouldn't but just thinking about that.
Well I can't help but touch myself.
I said all those things that yours was the best cock and it feels so good inside me that nobody's ever fucked me as good as you.
Touch me daddy.
Your fingers are right on my hot little button.
I feel slippery wet.
I know what's wrong.
I can't help it.
But daddy it's true.
Daddy your hand feels so good.
All those things I said were true.
My husband he doesn't come close.
Are you kidding me?
I've never ever ever felt that amazing.
Your cock touched touched me in places that my husband has never and he's never ever been able to make me come like that.
Not even when we role play.
Which seems kind of embarrassing to admit to my own dad.
His fingers are inside me.
But yes it's true.
I've always had to play daddy daughter with him because it turns me on so much.
It's what I need in order to get off with him.
And maybe there's been a deeper reason all along.
Deeper and deeper.
Keep touching me daddy.
I shouldn't be thinking about this.
I shouldn't be thinking about the fact that my dad has his fingers buried inside me.
Do you feel it daddy?
Your cock come from last night still inside your daughter.
It shouldn't turn me on so much but it does.
I know this is wrong.
But daddy I can't help it.
Maybe there's something inside me that has always needed you.
Oh yes.
I didn't know that we could get caught.
Do I want more?
I want more.
I need you.
Daddy I need your cock.
Inside me.
Just like last night.
Yeah daddy.
I know we have to be quick.
Everybody's downstairs.
I told my husband that I would be back after I talk to you.
But daddy I need you please.
Please.
Oh my god.
It's just like last night.
It's so wet every time.
You touch me in places that my husband never could.
No matter how hard you try.
You can never compare to my daddy.
Knowing that my daddy's bare cock is inside me.
How wrong it is.
How naughty it is.
But how good it feels.
Just like it's meant to be.
Isn't that right daddy?
There's a reason.
You stretch me so well.
My pussy accommodates for your thickness and your length.
It's because you're my daddy.
And you know what else daddy?
You know what's so naughty?
What's so wrong?
You're right here.
Fucking me.
Having sex with your daughter.
You're taking another man's wife.
That's right.
And now my perfect married pussy is all that you're ever going to be thinking about.
Isn't that right daddy?
My pussy's the only one.
You're going to daydream.
You're going to touch yourself.
To this moment now that's how it feels to be having sex.
Unprotected sex.
Raw sex.
With your own daughter.
Daddy, how does it feel?
Am I fucking me?
Yeah daddy, you're fucking me.
Oh my god, I have to admit.
I just can't enough myself.
I love pressing against you daddy.
Grinding my hips against you.
Pushing onto you.
So you can go deeper and deeper.
Giving your daughter the best sex she's ever had.
And I know that this is wrong.
I know I shouldn't say this out loud but daddy...
Daddy listen...
Are you listening daddy?
Are you listening?
What if...
You give me a baby daddy.
What if you really give me a baby?
What if you've already gotten me pregnant daddy?
Yeah daddy...
Because my husband...
You know he'll never do it.
He doesn't want a baby.
He never put one inside me.
He's not a real man like you daddy.
He doesn't compare to you at all.
Would you do it daddy?
Would you give me a baby daddy?
Would you be my baby daddy?
You'll have no idea.
We'll do it.
Right behind his back.
Yeah daddy.
He won't know...
That we're secretly fucking.
That you're the one that's gonna put a baby inside me.
You'll have no fucking clue.
You'll take another man's wife from right under his nose.
Even...
If it's your own daughter.
Right daddy?
Yeah.
Daddy.
You'll have no idea.
That I'm a daddy's girl now.
Right daddy?
Daddy.
Don't you want to come inside me again?
Fuck your comf, deeper and deeper inside.
Your sweet daughter.
Yeah.
Daddy.
Come with me daddy.
Give me a baby daddy.
He knows what you want.
Oh daddy.
Come for me daddy.
Oh my god.
My real dad is fucking me.
My real dad.
Is making me come.
Is fucking...
Deep inside my pussy.
Yeah.
Daddy.
Daddy keep going.
Please don't stop.
Keep pumping daddy.
Just like that daddy.
I love feeling your cock pulls and switch.
My dad.
Every last drop.
Every last drop of your cum daddy.
You filled my cum.
You filled my pussy with your cum again.
I can't even speak right.
And no.
I'm not tipsy still.
Daddy.
This is everything.
This is everything I ever needed.
Isn't this so nice?
Will you stay with me daddy?
Can we cuddle?
I can't believe this is happening but that's the best thing.
I know it daddy.
I love you.
I love you daddy.
I love you so much.
Doesn't it feel nice?
But that has a new ring to it.
Our love.